

# Changhun Lee

#### ROBOT ENGINEER · FIRMWARE SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Sanboncheon-ro 119-9, Gunpo-si, GyonugGi-do, 15816, Rep. of KOREA

□ (+82) 10-3659-8205 | Ich2895@naver.com | □ CH\_Lee

"Hope for the world."

## Summary.

I'm Changhun Lee, who want to become Wearable Robot Engineer. My research interest are wearable robot (Soft exoskelton, Hard exoskelton, etc.) for muscle strength and rehabilitation, HRI, Manipulator, Humanoid, Control System and Firmware. I would like to help disabled people with my technology and make a world where everyone can be happy.

### Research Interets

Wearable Robot Soft & Hard Exoskelton

**HRI** Haptic

**Humanoid** Humanoid & Manipulator

## **Education**

**KwangWoon University** 

Seoul, S.Korea

B.S. IN SCHOOL OF ROBOTICS

Mar. 2016 - Feb. 2022(Expected)

• Total GPA: 4.00/4.50 Major GPA: 4.12/4.50

• Club: BARAM(Robotics Academic Group) - [2020 Club president]

## Work Experience \_\_\_

#### KIST(Korea Institute of Science and Technology)

Seoul, S.Korea

STUDENT INTERN(ADVISOR DR. DONGHYUN HWANG)

Sep. 2020 - Feb. 2021

- Research on HaptiCube.
- Research on Pose estimation with magnetic sensor
- · Participate in Smartfarm auto-driving system Project

#### Sunduck High school Seoul, S.Korea

• Firmware Software Education(Arduino).

Filliwate Software Education(Aldullio

• 3D modeling Education.

Jun. 2020 - Sep. 2020

#### **Honors & Awards**

#### **AWARDS**

TEACHER

2019.12 **Finalist**, [17th] The World Embeded Software Contest 2019

Seoul, S.Korea

2020.08 3rd Place, Cham-bit Award

Kwangwoon univ.

2020.08 **Top**, The first semester of the third grade

Seoul, S.Korea

#### **HONORS**

2020.09 Full tuition Scholarship, For Top seat last semester

Seoul, S.Korea

#### Skills\_\_\_\_

**Programming** C/C++, Python, Matlab **Framework** Solidworks, Catia

DevOps ROS

Devops ROS

Languages Korean, English

## **Extracurricular Activity**

#### **Smart Factory with autocharge-scheduling**

Seoul, S.Korea

HARDWARE MODELING & DESIGN CLOSE LOOP CONTROL SYSTEM

May. 2019 - Dec. 2019

- 17th The World Embeded Software Contest 2019 project
- · A system for efficiently operating a mobile robot used in a factory in consideration of the remaining battery, workload, etc.
- Modeling mobile robots, factory and Designing Close loop System to Control System
- The source code related to this project is on my Github

#### Smart Walker[Cham-bit award]

Seoul, S.Korea

Dec. 2019 - Oct. 2020

HARDWARE MODELING & DESIGN CLOSE LOOP CONTROL SYSTEM

Kwangwoon Univ.'s Cham-bit award project

- I wanted to prevent traffic accidents for the elderly..
- Walker to ensure the safety of the elderly people
- Regardless of the terrain, it speeds up at a constant speed.
- The source code related to this project is on my Github

**Javis** Seoul, S.Korea

PERSONAL PROJECT

Aug. 2020 - Nov. 2020

- Mobile manipulator for helping disabled people
- To implement more diverse behaviors, The manipulator has 6DOF.
- To study ROS, all systems are implemented in ROS.
- The source code related to this project is on my **Github**

HaptiCube Seoul, S.Korea

KIST PROJECT Aug. 2020 - Dec. 2020

- I implement simulations for interaction between HaptiCube and people.
- · Based on OpenGL, there is a version that utilizes Computer Vision and a version that is based on visual effects.
- The source code related to this project is on my Github

SmartFarm Seoul, S.Korea

KIST project Sep. 2020 - Nov. 2020

- Creating a auto-driving robot to help Korean melon farm workers.
- All systems are implemented in ROS.
- The source code related to this project is on my Github

Magnet Pose Estimation Seoul, S.Korea

KIST PROJECT Dec. 2020 - Feb. 2021

- We implement a magnet sensor system to follow the location of continuum mechanism
- The source code related to this project is on my Github

## **Publication**

#### INTERNATIONAL

**AIM2021,** Development of an Embedded Sensor System for a 5-DOF Finger-wearable Tactile Interface", by Byeongkyu Lim, Changhun Lee, Donghyun Hwang

IEEE/ASME AIM

MARCH 5, 2021